asiasat.com 2019-06-22

# Privacy Policy | AsiaSat

The Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Cap 486) ("Ordinance") regulates the use of personal data relating to individuals collected in Hong Kong by data users. This Privacy Policy is made in accordance with the Ordinance and sets out how we use personal information provided by you through our website.

IP ADDRESSES

When browsing the AsiaSat website, your IP address (the unique address that identifies your computer on the internet) will be automatically logged by our web server. IP address information is used to allow us to compile general statistics and broad demographic information about our website, such as the daily number of visitors to our site. Such general statistics may be shared with our affiliates or subsidiaries and will be used to improve our website and services. No personal information will be collected about you (i.e. your identity will remain anonymous).

COOKIE POLICY

This site may use cookies to retrieve information about a visitor to the site. Cookies are data files stored on your browser. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if you prefer, you can change the Internet Options or preference settings on your web browser to prevent this. Cookies collected (if any) may be used by AsiaSat to compile general statistics about the number of visitors to our site or to improve and update our website, and such information may be shared with our affiliates or subsidiaries for the purposes of improving our service to you.  AsiaSat does not collect information from cookies sufficient to identify any individual nor does it use cookies to process personal data as defined by the Ordinance.

COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

On our website, you are given the option of contacting us online, either via email or by filling in a contact form. You are under no obligation to provide this information. The information that you send us may include your name, title, email address, etc. Such information will be kept strictly confidential as required by the Ordinance and will not be disclosed by us to anyone outside of AsiaSat in a form that would identify you without your prior consent unless it is required by law.

You agree that personal information that you provide to AsiaSat may be used as follows:

  1. for the purposes of processing your enquiry and improving our services to you or our website generally;
  2. providing you with regular communications from us regarding AsiaSat and its services, or the satellite industry generally;
  3. investigation of complaints or suspected suspicious activities;
  4. prevention or detection of crime;
  5. disclosure as permitted or required by law, regulation or government agency;
  6. aggregated statistics or behavioural analysis; and
  7. other purposes directly relating to any of the above.

From time to time, with your consent, except to the extent you have already opted out or in future opt out, we may use your personal information for direct marketing to you or your company in relation to business opportunities between your company and AsiaSat.  You can withdraw your consent, or ‘opt-out’ from any such direct marketing at any time by contacting us on the address or email address below.

We will erase or de-identify your personal information when they are no longer needed for any of the purposes stated above.

DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Any personal data held by AsiaSat is treated as confidential and shall only be disclosed as required to satisfy the purpose for which the data was collected (or a directly related purpose) as follows:

  1. to AsiaSat’s parent company, subsidiaries or companies controlled by or under common control with AsiaSat;
  2. government and regulatory authorities, law enforcement agencies or similar;
  3. AsiaSat’s legal advisors or other professional advisors; or
  4. a person or company acting by or on behalf of AsiaSat in the normal course of our business, such as for data management or distribution of mailing material.

COMMENTS

In accordance with the Ordinance (and subject to the exemptions therein), you have the right to ascertain whether AsiaSat holds your personal data, access such data (if any) and obtain copies, and/or correct any inaccuracies in the personal information held by AsiaSat about you at any time and request AsiaSat to cease to use your personal data at any point without charge. You can also opt-out from receiving direct marketing materials from us at any time. Should you wish to do so, or if you have any enquiries about our privacy policy, please write to us at:

**Asia Satellite Telecommunications Company Limited**

Privacy Compliance Officer  
12/F, Harbour Centre, 25 Harbour Road,  
Wanchai, Hong Kong  
Tel: (852) 2500 0888  
Fax: (852) 2500 0895  
Email: [privacy@asiasat.com](mailto:as-mkt@asiasat.com)

OTHER WEBSITES

This website may contain links to other websites. The privacy policies of those websites are not covered by this privacy policy and you are advised to check the privacy policies of those websites before using them.

DATA SECURITY

No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and while we will use all reasonable  efforts and take all practicable steps to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and any such transmission is therefore done at your own risk.

UPDATES OR REVISIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY

AsiaSat reserves the right to revise or update this policy at any time without notice. You are advised to review this policy on a regular basis. If AsiaSat decides to update, revise, modify or amend this policy, AsiaSat will post those changes to this webpage and/or other places AsiaSat deems appropriate.
